Henry F. Dobyns Papers 1732-2009 (bulk 1950-2000)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series V: Cornell Peru Project Files, 1943-1980
  - Subseries 3: Research Data Files, 1960-1969
    - Bolivia- IBM marginals, undated (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Bolivia- Interviewer data, 1965 (Box 155, Folder 17-18)
    - Bolivia- Interviewer data, 1965 (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - Bolivia- Interviewer reports, 1965 (Box 156, Folder 2-7)
    - Bolivia- Kami Mine, 1966 (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Bolivia- Markets Gumucio, 1964 (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - Bolivia- Miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Bolivia- Open ended questions, undated (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - Bolivia- Patients attended, undated (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Bolivia- Santa Cruz colonies, 1965 (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - Bolivia- Social structure scale, 1965-1966 (Box 156, Folder 14-15)
    - Bolivia- Social structure scale, undated (Box 156, Folder 16-18)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 157)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 158)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 159)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 160)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 161)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 162)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 163)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 164)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 165)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 166)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 167)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 168)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 169)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 170)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 171)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 172)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 173)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 174)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 175)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 176)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 177)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 178)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 179)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 180)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 181)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 182)
    - Bolivia- Values questionnaires, 1965 (Box 183)
    - Bolivia- Village Comparative Study, 1966 (Box 184, Folder 1-2)
    - Bolivia- Vital statistics, Caranavi, Carrasco, 1964 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Bolivia- Vital statistics, Sabaya, Oruro, 1964 (Box 184, Folder 4-5)
    - Code Keys, undated (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Ecuador- Community Inventory, undated (Box 184, Folder 7-9)
    - Peru- Census, undated (Box 184, Folder 10-11)
    - Peru- Census, Caracas, undated (Box 184, Folder 12)
    - Peru- Census, Chaquicocha, undated (Box 184, Folder 13-14)
    - Peru- Census, Mito, undated (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Peru- Census, Mito, undated (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Peru- Census questionnaires, undated (Box 185, Folder 2-3)
    - Peru- Code book, Checras, 1964 (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Peru- Code books, undated (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Peru- Coding sheets, 1965-1966 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Peru- Family Life Study questionnaires, 1960 (Box 185, Folder 7-9)
    - Peru- Hacienda analysis and card key, undated (Box 185, Folder 10)
    - Peru- Huaraz school study, 1963 (Box 185, Folder 11)
    - Peru- El Indice Alfabético del Atlas Comunal, 1964 (Box 185, Folder 12)
    - Peru- Indigenous community interviews with Personeros in Lima, 1962 (Box 185, Folder 13)
    - Peru- Indigenous community surveys, undated (Box 185, Folder 14-15)
    - Peru- Miscellaneous, undated (Box 185, Folder 16)
    - Peru- Notes, undated (Box 185, Folder 17)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, 1962-1964 (Box 185, Folder 18-19)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, 1962-1964 (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Peru- social structure scale, 1965 (Box 186, Folder 2-4)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Bolognesi, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 6-7)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Calca, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Canchis, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Concepción, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 10-11)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Cuzco, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 12)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Huancavelica, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 13-14)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Huánuco, 1969 (Box 186, Folder 15)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Lambayeque, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Lima, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 2-3)
    - Peru- Social structure scale, Pasco, 1969 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Peru- Urban area of Palca, 1964 (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Peru- Questionnaires, 1962 (Box 187, Folder 6-14)
    - Peru- Questionnaires, undated (Box 188, Folder 1-12)
    - Peru- Questionnaires, undated (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Peru- Questionnaires, Jucul, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 2-8)
    - Puerto Rico- Blank questionnaires, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rico- Coding forms, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Puerto Rico- Community analysis, La Cuesta- Montería, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rico- Community profiles, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 12-14)
    - Puerto Rico- Community reports, La Cuesta- Montería, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Puerto Rico- Community reports, Demajagua- Macho, 1964 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - Puerto Rico- Community reports, Limaní, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Puerto Rico- Community reports, Viví Abajo- Caonilla, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 2-3)
    - Puerto Rico- Economics and Land Tenure, Limaní, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 4)
    - Puerto Rico- Family Summaries, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 5)
    - Puerto Rico- Genealogical trees, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 6)
    - Puerto Rico- Genealogical trees- Viví Abajo- Caonilla, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 7)
    - Puerto Rico- Historical and Demographic Data, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 8)
    - Puerto Rico- Hospital records, Caonillas- Viví Abajo, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 9)
    - Puerto Rico- Hospital records, Demajagua- Macho, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 10)
    - Puerto Rico- Hospital records, Limaní, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 11-12)
    - Puerto Rico- Hospital records, spreadsheets, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 13)
    - Puerto Rico- Interviews, La Cuesta, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 14)
    - Puerto Rico- Photographic income, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 15)
    - Puerto Rico- Politics, Limaní, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 16)
    - Puerto Rico- Ramos-Bourne Questionnaires, 1932 (Box 190, Folder 17)
    - Puerto Rico- Spiritism analysis, Limaní and Viví Abajo, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 18)
    - Puerto Rico- Standard of Living, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 19)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Caonillas, 1964 (Box 190, Folder 20-21)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Caonillas, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 1-2)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, La Cuesta, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 3-8)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Demajagua, 1964 (Box 191, Folder 9-12)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Demajagua, 1964 (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Limaní Abajo, 1964 (Box 192, Folder 2-4)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Limaní Arriba, 1964 (Box 192, Folder 5-9)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, El Macho, 1964 (Box 192, Folder 10-12)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, El Macho, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 1-3)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Montería, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 4-7)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, El Muerto, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 8-12)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Spiritism, 1964 (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Puerto Rico- Questionnaires, Viví Abajo, 1964 (Box 194, Folder 1-4)
  - Subseries 4: Research Files, 1943-1968
    This subseries contains research material related to Peru, Bolivia, Puerto Rico, Thailand and other South American countries. Boxes 194-195.
    - Archivo Arzobispal de Lima, 1963 (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Arequipa notes, 1967 (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Charts, undated (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Chimborazo province, Ecuador, undated (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Colquiri, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Comibol archives, undated (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Comibol archives document lists, undated (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Fulbright scholars to US, 1966-1967 (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Grandule Cultivation, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 13)
    - Huapra massacre, 1960 (Box 194, Folder 14)
    - Lima migration sources, 1961 (Box 194, Folder 15)
    - Maps, 1959-1962 (Box 194, Folder 16)
    - Ministerio de Trabajo y Asuntos Indigenas, 1958-1960 (Box 194, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous, 1943-1963 (Box 194, Folder 18)
    - Mita, undated (Box 194, Folder 19)
    - News clippings- Bolivia, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 20)
    - News clippings- Colonization and Comunidades Indigenas, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 21)
    - News clippings- Cornell Peru Project, 1963-1965 (Box 194, Folder 22)
    - News clippings- National politics June to July, 1965 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - News clippings- Peru comunidad Hacienda violencia, 1963 (Box 195, Folder 2-3)
    - News clippings- Peru university press clippings, 1960-1968 (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - News clippings- Puerto Rico, 1965 (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - News clippings- Quito Congreso Indigenista, 1964 (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - News clippings- US AID to Latin America, 1965 (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Peasant massacres, 1959-1960 (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - PNIPA, 1959-1963 (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Pueblo Libre, 1953-1963 (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Puerto Rico, 1963-1964 (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Puerto Rico coffee cultivation, 1964 (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Puerto Rico land deeds, 1964 (Box 195, Folder 13)
    - Sayan, Peru, 1964-1965 (Box 195, Folder 14)
    - Spiritism literature for analysis, 1964 (Box 195, Folder 15)
    - Vicos, undated (Box 195, Folder 16)
- Series VI: Academic Files, 1947-1997
  This series contains material related to Henry F. Dobyns’ academic career including his graduate education and teaching career. This series is divided into 7 subseries. The material is arranged alphabetically. This series contains restrictions on materials in box 205 folder 15 and box 207 folders 9 and 17-31.
  - Subseries 1: Cornell University, 1951-1966
    This subseries contains course and teaching material from Dobyns’ doctoral education. Boxes 195-198.
    - American Anthropological Association meeting expenses, 1962 (Box 195, Folder 17)
    - Anthropology 202- Anthropology in the Modern World, 1964 (Box 195, Folder 18-20)
    - Anthropology 204, 1957 (Box 195, Folder 21)
    - Anthropology 281- Middle and South America, 1959-1960 (Box 196, Folder 1-2)
    - Anthropology 332- Ethnology of Middle and South America, 1963 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Anthropology 411- Cultural Anthropology, 1956 (Box 196, Folder 4-5)
    - Anthropology 412- Cultural Change, 1957 (Box 196, Folder 6-10)
    - Anthropology 482- Applied Anthropology, 1963 (Box 196, Folder 11)
    - Anthropology 482- Applied Anthropology, 1965 (Box 196, Folder 12)
    - Anthropology 482- Applied Anthropology, 1966 (Box 196, Folder 13)
    - Anthropology 482- Applied Anthropology- Social Change Handbook, 1966 (Box 196, Folder 14-15)
    - Anthropology 482- Applied Anthropology- Social Change Handbook, 1966 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Anthropology 604- Native Peoples of the World, undated (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Anthropology 622- Comparative Religious Systems, 1954 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Anthropology 624- Comparative Economic Systems of non- Western Peoples, undated (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Anthropology 675- Anthropological Theory and Method, 1956 (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Anthropology 676- Anthropological Theory, 1957 (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Anthropology 681- Culture and Culture Change in Middle and South America, undated (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Anthropology 684, 1953-1954 (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Anthropology 690, 1954 (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Course schedules, 1962-1963 (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Dissertation draft, undated (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Far Eastern Studies 501-502- Contemporary India, 1955 (Box 197, Folder 12-15)
    - Field laboratory in Applied Anthropology, 1952 (Box 197, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1952-1965 (Box 197, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous course materials, undated (Box 197, Folder 18)
    - Notes, 1956-1957 (Box 197, Folder 19)
    - Sociology 201- Research Methods in Behavioral Science, 1953-1954 (Box 198, Folder 1-3)
    - Sociology 201- Research Methods in Behavioral Science, 1954-1955 (Box 198, Folder 4-8)
    - Sociology 202- Experimental Methods, 1954 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Sociology 431- American Society, 1953-1954 (Box 198, Folder 10-11)
    - Sociology- Anthropology Club Bulletin, 1962-1964 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Southwest Project, 1951-1954 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Stirling County Study, 1951-1953 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Stirling County Study, 1954-1958 (Box 198, Folder 15)
  - Subseries 2: Newberry Library, 1978-1997
    This subseries contains material mostly related to summer institutes at the Newberry Library funded by the National Endowment of the Humanities. Boxes 199-203.
    - Annual Bibliography of Recent books and articles in American Indian history, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Bibliographic guides, 1985-1988 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Chicago American Indian Oral History Project, 1983 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Conundrums and Complexities: Native American Water Rights Litigation, 1991 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - Educational study trip to the Northeast journal, 1979 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Energy Self-Sufficiency: Some vital first steps, 1980 (Box 199, Folder 6-8)
    - Fellows program, 1978-1991 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - History, 1996 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Indians in American History, 1985-1991 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Indoamerican Early Historic Trade in North America, 1980 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Memos, 1973-1981 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Memos, 1982-1991 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Annual report, 1981-1982 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Annual report, 1982-1983, 1984 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Application, 1980-1981 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Colloquium, 1981 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Final report, 1984 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Financial reports, 1981-1984 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project- Work logs, 1981-1983 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Application, 1983 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Bunte, Pamela, 1983-1984 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Expense receipts, 1983 (Box 199, Folder 26)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Final report, 1984 (Box 199, Folder 27)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Grumet, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box 199, Folder 28)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Hoxie, Frederick, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Jackson, Robert, 1982-1983 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Krech, Shepard III, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- McNeill, William, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Moore, John, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Participant papers, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Proposal drafts, 1982-1983 (Box 200, Folder 7-8)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project Conference- Schedule, 1983 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Cook, Noble David, 1983-1987 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Fowler, William, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Hoxie, Frederick, 1984-1987 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Jackson, Robert H., 1982-1987 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Jones, Kristine, 1983-1986 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Krech, Shepard III, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Lovell, W. George, 1982-1983 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Lovell, W. George, 1984-1986 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Moore, John, 1986 (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Native American Population Change, 1984 (Box 200, Folder 20-23)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Review, 1987 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Stoffle, Richard, 1983-1987 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Thornton, Russell, 1983-1986 (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Trimble, Michael, 1981-1986 (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Trout, Lawana, 1986 (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- Unidentified draft, undated (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- The Web of Disease, 1986-1987 (Box 201, Folder 5-15)
    - Native American Historic Demography Project manuscript- The Web of Disease, 1986-1987 (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Pueblo Librarians, 1979 (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - Research Proposal- Historic Population Trends among Tribal Peoples of the United States, 1981 (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - Research Proposal- Historic Population Trends among Tribal Peoples of the United States- Financial reports, 1982-1983 (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Research Proposal- Pueblo Indian Population and Settlement, 1581-1583, 1983 (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature, 1991-1994 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature- An Annotated Bibliography, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature- A Chronology of Events important in the Native North American Experience, 1997 (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature- Collectors of Native American Texts, 1991-1993 (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature- Major Native American Language Divisions, 1992 (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature- A Papago Woman’s Life in Historical Context, 1991-1993 (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Summer Institute in Native American Literature- Schedules, 1993 (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Summer Institute for US History Teachers, 1983-1989 (Box 202, Folder 13-14)
    - Summer Institute for US History Teachers- Population Exercise, 1988 (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Summer Institute for US History Teachers- Proposal drafts, 1984 (Box 202, Folder 16-17)
    - Summer Institute for US History Teachers- Readings, undated (Box 202, Folder 18)
    - Summer Institute for US History Teachers- Selected dates significant in US history and Native American History, 1986 (Box 202, Folder 19)
    - Summer Institute for US History Teachers- Three basic factors in Native American demography, 1987 (Box 202, Folder 20)
    - Tribal History Program, 1988-1990 (Box 202, Folder 21-23)
    - Tribal History Program- Calto, Penny, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 24)
    - Tribal History Program- Clark, Robey, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 25)
    - Tribal History Program- Dodge, Carol, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 26)
    - Tribal History Program- Fisher, Darlene, 1989-1990 (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Tribal History Program- Haymond, Jack, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - Tribal History Program- Lambeth, David, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Tribal History Program- Martinez, Glenabah, 1988 (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - Tribal History Program- Pavlik, Steve, 1988-1991 (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Tribal History Program- Szablewicz, John, 1989-1990 (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Tribal History Program- White Man, Harold, 1989 (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Tribalism Today, 1978 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Subseries 3: Prescott College, 1960-1977
    This subseries contains teaching and administrative material from Dr. Dobyns’ time as a professor of anthropology and later the Vice President of Academic Affairs. Also included are student research program materials. Boxes 203-207. This subseries contains restrictions on materials in box 205 folder 15 and box 207 folders 9 and 17-31.
    - Academic Council minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - Academic Council minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Administrative structure, 1970-1973 (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Admissions information, 1971-1972 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Advising guidance, 1970-1972 (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - American Philosophical Society grant, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Anthropology in the Contemporary World, 1972 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Applied Anthropology, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Alabama/Taladega, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Article concepts, 1969-1971 (Box 203, Folder 18)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Citation Index 1-5, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 19)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Citation Index 6-25, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 20)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Colombia, 1969-1972 (Box 203, Folder 21)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Common Research Problems, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 22)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Confidential Role as Researcher, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 23)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Ecuador, 1969-1971 (Box 203, Folder 24)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Evaluation Research, 1971 (Box 203, Folder 25)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Expanding Roles, 1969-1971 (Box 203, Folder 26)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Peru, 1963 (Box 203, Folder 27)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Strategic Intervention: Cornell, 1968-1971 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Applied Anthropology manuscript- Venezuela, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Archaeological field school, 1970-1973 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Belshaw, Michael, 1969-1973 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Brew, Douglas, 1970, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Catalogs, 1960-1973 (Box 204, Folder 6-7)
    - Center for Man and Environment, 1970-1972 (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Center for Man and Environment- Brochure, 1970-1971 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    - Center for Man and Environment- Budget, 1971-1973 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    - Center for Man and Environment- Curriculum, 1970-1972 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    - Center for Man and Environment- Fourth Southwestern Student Conference in Anthropology, undated (Box 204, Folder 12)
    - Center for Man and Environment- History, 1965, 1967 (Box 204, Folder 13)
    - Center for Man and Environment- Meeting notes, undated (Box 204, Folder 14)
    - Center for Man and Environment- Merit evaluation, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Centers, 1972 (Box 204, Folder 16)